she ends up on a hay bale and just goes
floating by and she's like I'm just
going to ride it and and I told her I
said get into a tree or
something and she goes down river and I
don't see her anymore but I hear her
yelling and then I take Grammy and I get
underneath her I get her up on my
shoulders and she swings her leg over a
tree limb and is saddled in a tree
limb and I tried to climb into that tree
and I was just there was I was so tired
I couldn't even I couldn't even lift
myself into that tree so I was just
hanging
on and I rested for a while and I
mustered up some
strength and emptied the water out of my
boots um and shimmed up that tree and me
and my mother-in-law
we we sat in that tree and watched this
thing come up and it came up their house
is gone like it it's still there it
moved it it picked up the her house and
moved it and smashed it into
trees and I could see my house
flooded and there's so much water around
us that we couldn't see anybody I didn't
know how everyone was
but we just lost everything our house
our house is trash we have our
vehicles but we didn't lose our life
thank
God and all I we were sitting on the
back of that shed and I don't know I
don't really what you believe is what
you believe that that's fine but I I
cried out to Jesus I said Lord you got
to help me cuz this is bad and I thought
maybe we could die I'm tell tell you it
was so
close so sorry folks I didn't stay safe
but we made it through
it we survived
it and so
now I don't know what we do
next the whole place is trash we don't
have a house
but we have our family when I saw my
wife she thought I was dead
[Music]
so some crazy stuff
but
sorry sorry about that but I'm a little
emotional about it I guess it's not
typical of me if you know me
but wow I almost died today
but everyone is okay everyone is okay we
made it we sat there in that tree for a
couple
hours just watching the water come at us
hoping that that tree would hold and it
did and we were just
praying
[Music]
and mother-in-law was upset that she's
missing her soap
opera we had a fun time in a tree I'll
send you a picture you all can post a
picture of the tree that saved my life
so anyway uh keep praying I'm going to
say that some prayer helped I know it
matters we live to tell the tale so
there you go anyway we'll see how the I
don't know even have I don't have a
clue what the next step
is but I I'm just happy that everyone's
okay so we'll we'll we'll say y to that
all right I'll keep you posted watch on
my Facebook I'm going to post pictures
of the the damage so you can see uh what
all just happened all right
[Music]